Stella you have to help me
what nonsense are you talking about
I didn't ask you to do anything
don't pin this on me
you ruined me
it's all your fault
stay away get off me pull him away from her
get off me it's all your fault
my office is not a place for you to make a stream
chairman I'm begging you give me another chance
I still have a mortgage of millions to pay off
I can't lose this job
you can't lose this job
if it weren't for my multi talented wife
you would have offended
all of our key business partners
then hundreds even thousands of employees
would lose their jobs and homes because of you
who are they supposed to cry to huh
you chose the wrong master
you did the wrong thing
now face the punishment
pack your things
go sleep under a bridge
I don't want to see you again
take him away
chairman I was wrong
Stella Ross made me do it
Benjamin Benjamin I really didn't mean to
I know I was wrong